Register of the Norwood F. Allman papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1943-1987
  - Hsiang, Ying (Folder 53)
  - Hsiao, Chen Ying (Folder 54)
  - Hsiao, Chia-chu (Folder 55)
  - Hsiao, Chih-chu (Folder 56)
  - Hsiao, Ching-kuang (Folder 57)
  - Hsiao, Fu-cheng (Folder 58)
  - Hsiao, Ke (Folder 59)
  - Hsiao, Lu-peng (Folder 60)
  - Hsiao, Shu-hsuan (Folder 61)
  - Hsiao, Sin-yu (Folder 62)
  - Hsiao, T. T. (Folder 63)
  - Hsieh, Chia-lin (Folder 64)
  - Hsieh, Chieh-shih (Folder 65)
  - Hsieh, Chien (Folder 66)
  - Hsieh, Chin-yuan (Folder 67)
  - Hsieh, Hsueh-hung (Folder 68)
  - Hsieh, Kang-che (Folder 69)
  - Hsieh, Kuan-sheng (Folder 70)
  - Hsieh, Pao-chiao (Folder 71)
  - Hsieh, Shou-kang (Folder 72)
  - Hsieh, Teh-yi (Folder 73)
  - Hsien, Chih (Folder 74)
  - Hsu, Chang (Folder 75)
  - Hsu, Chi-chin (Folder 76)
  - Hsu, Chi-chuang (Folder 77)
  - Hsu, Chien-ping (Folder 78)
  - Hsu, Chien-ting (Folder 79)
  - Hsu, Chi-hsiang (Folder 80)
  - Hsu, Ching-chih (Folder 81)
  - Hsu, Chung-chih (Folder 82)
  - Hsu, Feng-tsao (Folder 83)
  - Hsu, Fu-lin (Folder 84)
  - Hsu, Hsiang-chien (Folder 85)
  - Hsu, Hsiao-yen (Folder 86)
  - Hsu, Jen Chen (Folder 87)
  - Hsu, Kan (Folder 88)
  - Hsu, Konrad (Folder 89)
  - Hsu, Kung-su (Folder 90)
  - Hsu, Kuo-chen (Folder 91)
  - Hsu, Leonard S. (Folder 92)
  - Hsu, Liang (Folder 93)
  - Hsu, Mien-tang (Folder 94)
  - Hsu, Mo (Folder 95)
  - Hsu, Nien-tsing (Folder 96)
  - Hsu, Pei-ken (Folder 97)
  - Hsu, Po-yuan (Folder 98)
  - Hsu, Pu-cheng (Folder 99)
  - Hsu, Shao-ching (Folder 100)
  - Hsu, Shao-tsung (Folder 101)
  - Hsu, Shih-chang (Folder 102)
  - Hsu, Shih-lien (Folder 103)
  - Hsu, Shih-ying (Folder 104)
  - Hsu, Shih-yu (Folder 105)
  - Hsu, Shu-tseng (Folder 106)
  - Hsu, Ta-chien (Folder 107)
  - Hsu, Tao-ling (Folder 108)
  - Hsu, Ting-yao (Folder 109)
  - Hsu, Tsao-shih (Folder 110)
  - Hsu, Wei-hsin (Folder 111)
  - Hsu, Wen-huan (Folder 112)
  - Hsu, Yang-chih (Folder 113)
  - Hsu, Yeh (Folder 114)
  - Hsu, Yen-kang (Folder 115)
  - Hsu, Yuan-chuan (Folder 116)
  - Hsu, Yuan-teh (Folder 117)
  - Hsu, Yun (Folder 118)
  - Hsu, Yung-chang (Folder 119)
  - Hsuan, Tieh-wu (Folder 120)
  - Hsueh, Tu-pi (Folder 121)
  - Hsueh, Wen-po (Folder 122)
  - Hsueh, Yueh (Folder 123)
  - Hu, Chia-chi (Folder 124)
  - Hu, Feng (Folder 125)
  - Hu, Han-min (Folder 126)
  - Hu, I-sheng (Folder 127)
  - Hu, Jo-yu (Folder 128)
  - Hu, Lan-cheng (Folder 129)
  - Hu, Lan-sheng (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hu, Lien (Folder 2)
  - Hu, Lin (Folder 3)
  - Hu, Mu-lan (Folder 4)
  - Hu, S. K. (Folder 5)
  - Hu, Shih (Folder 6)
  - Hu, Shih-tse (Folder 7)
  - Hu, Shu-hua (Folder 8)
  - Hu, Tao-wei (Folder 9)
  - Hu, Tieh (Folder 10)
  - Hu, Tseng-chun (Folder 11)
  - Hu, Tsung-nan (Folder 12)
  - Hu, Wei (Folder 13)
  - Hu, Yu-kun (Folder 14)
  - Hua, Chen-lin (Folder 16)
  - Hua, Wen-kuan (Folder 17)
  - Huang, Chen-chiu (Folder 18)
  - Huang, Chiang (Folder 19)
  - Huang, Chiao-yu (Folder 20)
  - Huang, Chi-hsiang (Folder 21)
  - Huang, Chih-luh (Folder 22)
  - Huang, Fu (Folder 23)
  - Huang, Fu-sheng (Folder 24)
  - Huang, Fu-tsun (Folder 25)
  - Huang, Harry W. (Folder 26)
  - Huang, Hsiang-ku (Folder 27)
  - Huang, Hsiao-ping (Folder 28)
  - Huang, Hsing (Folder 29)
  - Huang, Hsu-chu (Folder 30)
  - Huang, Jen-ling (Folder 31)
  - Huang, Kuang-jui (Folder 32)
  - Huang, Li-kwei (Folder 33)
  - Huang, Lin (Folder 34)
  - Huang, Lin-shu (Folder 35)
  - Huang, Ma-pi (Folder 36)
  - Huang, Mu-sung (Folder 37)
  - Huang, Nan-peng (Folder 38)
  - Huang, Pen-jen (Folder 39)
  - Huang, Pin-heng (Folder 40)
  - Huang, Quentin (Folder 41)
  - Huang, Shao-hsiung (Folder 42)
  - Huang, Tao (Folder 43)
  - Huang, Tao-hui (Folder 44)
  - Huang, Ta-wei (Folder 45)
  - Huang, Tze-hsiu (Folder 46)
  - Huang, Tzu-hsiang (Folder 47)
  - Huang, Wei (Folder 48)
  - Huang, Y. T. (Folder 49)
  - Huang, Yen Pei (Folder 50)
  - Huang, Yu-shen (Folder 51)
  - Huber (Folder 52)
  - Huizer, Marcia (Folder 53)
  - Huizer, Peter (Folder 54)
  - Huldermann, Paul F. (Folder 55)
  - Hull, A. T. (Folder 56)
  - Hull, Edward (Folder 57)
  - Hung, C. C. (Folder 58)
  - Hung, Lu-tung (Folder 59)
  - Hunt, William P. (Folder 60)
  - Hunter, Edward (Folder 61)
  - Huntington, Archer S. (Folder 62)
  - Hutton, William (Folder 63)
  - Hwa, William Z. (Folder 64)
  - Hwang, William C. T. (Folder 65)
  - Hymoff, Edward (Folder 66)
  - Hynn, Man K. (Folder 67)
  - Ide, Misao (Folder 68)
  - Iida, Shojiro (Folder 69)
  - Iino, Takeo (Folder 70)
  - Ikeda, Seihin (Folder 71)
  - Imamura, Hitoshi (Folder 72)
  - Imhoff, Rupert (Folder 73)
  - Indian diplomats, military and public figures, statesmen (Folder 74)
  - Ino, Ei-ichi (Folder 75)
  - Ino, Hiroyasu (Folder 76)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations (Folder 77)
  - International Suppliers, Limited (Folder 78)
  - Inukai, Ken (Folder 79)
  - I Pao-san (Folder 80)
  - Irwin, Vladimir (Folder 81)
  - Isaacs, Harold R. (Folder 82)
  - Ishaki, Ayas (Folder 83)
  - Ishiguro, Tadaatsu (Folder 84)
  - Ishihara, Koichi (Folder 85)
  - Ishiwata, Sotaro (Folder 86)
  - Israel, Joseph (Folder 87)
  - Itagaki, Seishiro (Folder 88)
  - Iturbe, Raymon (Folder 89)
  - Iturralde (Folder 90)
  - Jack, C. D. (Folder 91)
  - Jaffe, Philip (Folder 92)
  - Janney, Robert S. (Folder 93)
  - Japanese Cabinet, October 9, 1945 (Folder 94)
  - Japanese control of aluminum in the Far East (Folder 95)
  - Japanese diplomats, military and public figures, statesmen (Folder 96)
  - Japanese diplomats, military and public figures, statesmen (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Japanese espionage and secret service operations during World War II (Folder 4-5)
  - Japanese prison camps in Hong Kong, 1941-42 (Folder 6)
  - Jayanam, Nai Direk (Folder 7)
  - Jen, Shan-hsueh (Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Ernest (Folder 9)
  - Johnson, William (Folder 10)
  - Jones, Alfred (Folder 11)
  - Jones, Joseph A. (Folder 12)
  - Jurika, Blanche (Folder 13)
  - Kagoshima, Torao (Folder 14)
  - Kahin & Carmody (Folder 15)
  - Kaloushin, Alex (Folder 16)
  - Kamimura, Shin-ichi (Folder 17)
  - Kan, Chieh-ho (Folder 18)
  - Kan, Chao-hsi (Folder 19)
  - Kan, Li-chu (Folder 20)
  - Kan, Nai-kuang (Folder 21)
  - Kanady, Dilmus (Folder 22)
  - Kang, Hsuan (Folder 23)
  - Kang, J. K. (Folder 24)
  - Kang, Ke-chin (Folder 25)
  - Kang, Pen-po (Folder 26)
  - Kang, Sheng (Folder 27)
  - Kang, Tai-kuang (Folder 28)
  - Kang, Tseh (Folder 29)
  - Kang, Yu-wei (Folder 30)
  - Kanji Teleprinter (Folder 31)
  - Kao, Chun-ting (Folder 32)
  - Kao, Chun-ting (Folder 33)
  - Kao, Fang (Folder 34)
  - Kao, I-han (Folder 35)
  - Kao, Kang (Folder 36)
  - Kao, Kuan-wu (Folder 37)
  - Kao, Kuang (Folder 38)
  - Kao, Kwei-tzu (Folder 39)
  - Kao, Ling-wei (Folder 40)
  - Kao, Ping-fang (Folder 41)
  - Kao, Shu-hsiung (Folder 42)
  - Kao, Ssu-chien (Folder 42)
  - Kao, Suan-chen (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kao, Tsung-wu (Folder 2)
  - Kao, Yu-tung (Folder 3)
  - Karatchoff (Folder 4)
  - Karsch, D. (Folder 5)
  - Kashiwamura, Tozhizo (Folder 6)
  - Katsu, Hirao (Folder 7)
  - Kawabe, Shozo (Folder 8)
  - Ke, Ching-en (Folder 9)
  - Ke, Ting-yuan (Folder 10)
  - Ke, Tze-chuan (Folder 11)
  - Keng, Tse (Folder 12)
  - Kenney, George (Folder 13)
  - Kessler, George (Folder 14)
  - Keswick, John (Folder 15)
  - Khalka, Duke of (Folder 16)
  - Khan, Abdul (Folder 17)
  - Kheiri, Sathar (Folder 18)
  - Ki, Chang-chih (Folder 19)
  - Kimura, Masamichi (Folder 20)
  - Kinney, Henry W. (Folder 21)
  - Kiang, Piao (Folder 22)
  - King, L. C. (Folder 23)
  - King, P. Z. (Folder 24)
  - Kinney, Charles B. (Folder 25)
  - Kirschbaum, H. (Folder 26)
  - Kissell, Michael (Folder 27)
  - Kita, Reikichi (Folder 28)
  - Kita, Seiichi (Folder 29)
  - Kluck, Martin (Folder 30)
  - Ko, Chuang Fa (Folder 31)
  - Ko, Pao-chuan (Folder 32)
  - Koga, Mineichi (Folder 33)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred (Folder 34-35)
  - Kolpakoff, Anatole (Folder 36)
  - Konstantinoff, M. A. (Folder 37)
  - Koo, Teh-chang (Folder 38)
  - Koo, Y. C. (Folder 39)
  - Kordt, Erich (Folder 40)
  - Korean diplomats, military and public figures, statesmen (Folder 41-42)
  - Kosret, Stien (Folder 43)
  - Kotewall, Robert (Folder 44)
  - Kovid, Luang (Folder 45)
  - Kramer, Johanna (Folder 46)
  - Krapf, Franz (Folder 47)
  - Kretschner, General (Folder 48)
  - Kries, Von (Folder 49)
  - Krivoss, Boris (Folder 50)
  - Kroeger, A. R. (Folder 51)
  - Ku, Cheng-kang (Folder 52)
  - Ku, Cheng-lun (Folder 53)
  - Ku, Ching-tien (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Ku, Chi-wu (Folder 2)
  - Ku, Chu-tung (Folder 3)
  - Ku, Chung-chen (Folder 4)
  - Ku, Chung-shan (Folder 5)
  - Ku, L. S. (Folder 6)
  - Ku, Meng-yu (Folder 7)
  - Ku, Pao-heng (Folder 8)
  - Ku, Shu-li (Folder 9)
  - Ku, Tzu-heng (Folder 10)
  - Ku, Wei-chun (Folder 11)
  - Ku, Yi-chun (Folder 12)
  - Ku, Ying-fen (Folder 13)
  - Ku, Yu-hsiu (Folder 14)
  - Kuan, Hsiang-ying (Folder 15)
  - Kuan, Lin-cheng (Folder 16)
  - Kuang, Ping-sheng (Fong, B. S.) (Folder 16A)
  - Kudlaenko, General (Folder 17)
  - Kuether, Klaus (Folder 18)
  - Kuhrt, H. D. (Folder 19)
  - Kum, T. S. (Folder 20)
  - Kung, Ching-teh (Folder 21)
  - Kung, Chu (Folder 22)
  - Kung, David (Folder 23)
  - Kung, H. H. (Folder 24)
  - Kung, Ho-cheng (Folder 25)
  - Kung, Hsiang (Folder 26)
  - Kung, Hsiang-hsi (Folder 27)
  - Kung, Kuo-liang (Folder 28)
  - Kung, L. T. (Folder 29)
  - Kung, Ling-shun (Folder 30)
  - Kunjara, Mom Luang (Folder 31)
  - Kuo, Chan (Folder 32)
  - Kuo, Chi-chih (Folder 33)
  - Kuo, Chien (Folder 34)
  - Kuo, Chun-tao (Folder 35)
  - Kuo, Gin-chiu (Helena) (Folder 36)
  - Kuo, Ju-tung (Folder 37)
  - Kuo, Tse Fan (Folder 38)
  - Kuo, P. W. (Folder 39)
  - Kuo, Peng (Folder 40)
  - Kuo, Sze-yen (Folder 41)
  - Kuo, Tai-chi (Folder 42)
  - Kuo, Te-chun (Folder 43)
  - Kuo, Teh-chuan (Folder 44)
  - Kuo, Te-lin (Folder 45)
  - Kuo, Teh-lou (Folder 46)
  - Kuo, Wei-man (Folder 47)
  - Kurban, Ali (Folder 48)
  - Kuroda, Shigenori (Folder 49)
  - Kusaba, Tatsumi (Folder 50)
  - Kwan, C. S. (Folder 51)
  - Kwan, Chung-hai (Folder 52)
  - Kwoh, Frank (Folder 53)
  - Kwok, David (Folder 54)
  - Kwok, K. K. (Folder 55)
  - Kwok, Kam-kwan (Folder 56)
  - Kwong, Y. C. (Folder 57)
  - Labin, Suzanne (Folder 58)
  - Langdon, E. W. (Folder 59)
  - Laphanukrom, Nai Toa (Folder 60)
  - Laurel, Jose (Folder 61)
  - Leach, Dr. (Folder 62)
  - Leake, B. G. (Folder 63)
  - Lee, Duncan C. (Folder 64)
  - Lee, Tsung-dao (Folder 65)
  - Lee, William Yinson (Folder 66)
  - Lee and Li (Folder 67)
  - Lei, Chen (Folder 68)
  - Lenzer, Reuben (Folder 69)
  - Li, Chi-sen (Folder 70)
  - Li, Hsiang-fen (Folder 71)
  - Li, Kwoh-ting (Folder 72)
  - Li, Ming (Folder 73)
  - Li, Pao-kuang (Folder 74)
  - Li, Ta-chengo (Folder 75)
  - Li, Thian-hok (Folder 76)
  - Li, Tsung-jen (Folder 77-78)
  - Li, Wei (Folder 79)
  - Liang, Feng (Folder 80)
  - Liang, Shu-ming (Folder 81)
  - Lieu, Julius (Folder 82)
  - Lin, Keng-hsieh (Folder 83)
  - Lin, Tieh (Folder 84)
  - Lin, Tsu-han (Folder 85)
  - Lindsay, Lord (Folder 86)
  - Ling, Hong-chye (Folder 87)
  - Liu, Cheng-hua (Folder 88)
  - Liu, Chin-ho (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Liu, Dan (Folder 2)
  - Liu, Frederick Fu (Folder 3)
  - Liu, Hoh-tu (Folder 4)
  - Liu, Ju-ming (Folder 5)
  - Liu, Jun-yuan (Folder 6)
  - Liu, Kan (Folder 7)
  - Liu, Kung-lung (Folder 8)
  - Liu, Kwei-Tang (Folder 9)
  - Liu, La-tai (Folder 10)
  - Liu, Liang-mo (Folder 11)
  - Liu, Lu-yin (Folder 12)
  - Liu, Mao-en (Folder 13)
  - Liu, Maurice (Folder 14)
  - Liu, N. C. (Folder 15)
  - Liu, Nai-chien (Folder 16)
  - Liu, Nai-chun (Folder 17)
  - Liu, O. S. (Folder 18)
  - Liu, Pei-chun (Folder 19)
  - Liu, Pen-ho (Folder 20)
  - Liu, Po-chen (Folder 21)
  - Liu, Shao-chi (Folder 22)
  - Liu, Shang-chih (Folder 23)
  - Liu, Shang-ching (Folder 24)
  - Liu, Shi (Folder 25)
  - Liu, Shih-I (Folder 26)
  - Liu, Shih-shun (Folder 27)
  - Liu, Shih-yuan (Folder 28)
  - Liu, Shou-chung (Folder 29)
  - Liu, Teh-ming (Folder 30)
  - Liu, Tien-fu (Folder 31)
  - Liu, To-chuan (Folder 32)
  - Liu, Tsu-fan (Folder 33)
  - Liu, Tsu-sheng (Folder 34)
  - Liu, Tze-tan (Folder 35)
  - Liu, Wei-chih (Folder 36)
  - Liu, Wei-hui (Folder 37)
  - Liu, Yung-ming (Folder 38)
  - Livanova, Mrs. V. (Folder 39)
  - Lo, Lorenzo (Folder 40)
  - Loh, T. Y. (Folder 41)
  - Lu, Chih-wei (Folder 42)
  - Luang, Kriangsak Phichit (Folder 43)
  - Luang, Pridit (Folder 44)
  - Lucci, Enzo (Folder 45)
  - McBain, Bill (Folder 46)
  - McCann, Robert (Folder 47)
  - McCarthy, Joe (Folder 48)
  - McKenna, Royal (Folder 49)
  - McKim, John (Folder 50)
  - McTurk, Dave (Folder 51)
  - Ma, Pu-feng (Folder 52)
  - Ma, Yin-chu (Folder 53)
  - Mackensen, Paul (Folder 54)
  - Mahidol, Ananda (King of Siam) (Folder 55)
  - Maltzahn, Herr (Folder 56)
  - Manav Samaj (Folder 57)
  - Manudharm, Luang (Folder 58)
  - Mao, Chen-hua (Folder 59)
  - Mao, Fu-cheng (Folder 60)
  - Mao, Hung-pin (Folder 61)
  - Mao, Pang-chu (Folder 62)
  - Mao, Ping-wen (Folder 63)
  - Mao, Sung-liang (Folder 64)
  - Mao, Tse-tung (Folder 65)
  - Mao, Wei-shou (Folder 66)
  - Maps of China, Japan and other areas of East Asia (Folder 67)
  - Maraeini, Fosco (Folder 68)
  - Marden, George E. (Folder 69)
  - Margolis, Laura (Folder 70)
  - Marsman, Jan (Folder 71)
  - Marsoff, Natalia (Folder 72)
  - Matsinger, Harrison (Folder 73)
  - Matsuda, Reisuke (Folder 74)
  - Matsui, Keishiro (Folder 75)
  - Matsui, Takuro (Folder 76)
  - Matsuoka, Yosuke (Folder 77)
  - Matsushima, Kan (Folder 78)
  - Matthews, J. B. (Folder 79)
  - Maung Mya (Folder 80)
  - Maxon, Inc. (Folder 81)
  - Maxwell, James (Folder 82)
  - May, Captain (Folder 83)
  - May, O. (Folder 84)
  - Mayer, Rudolf (Folder 85)
  - Mehnert, Klaus (Folder 86)
  - Mei, Lan Fang (Folder 87)
  - Meisinger, Colonel (Folder 88)
  - Miao, Yun-tai (Folder 89)
  - Miles, Commander, Pattern for Personnel to be Used in China (Folder 90)
  - Minami, Jiro (Folder 91)
  - Miner, Charles S. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Misselwitz, Henry (Folder 2)
  - Mitchell, Kate (Folder 3)
  - Mitchell, Tom (Folder 4)
  - Miura, Binji (Folder 5)
  - Miura, Takeyoshi (Folder 6)
  - Mo, Sing-ya (Folder 7)
  - Mo, Te-hui (Folder 8)
  - Mo, Y. T. (Folder 9)
  - Mongkon, Prom Yoti (Folder 10)
  - Montgomery, Field Marshal (Folder 11)
  - Moore, Frederick (Folder 12)
  - Morioka, Susumu (Folder 13)
  - Morris, Robert (Folder 14)
  - Moss, Anni Lee (Folder 15)
  - Mou, Chung-heng (Folder 16)
  - Mow, P. T. (Folder 17)
  - Mow, Y. T. (Folder 18)
  - Moy, Ernest K.
    - General (Folder 19)
    - "A Chinese-American View of American Aid," Canton, March 26, 1949 (Folder 20)
    - "Douglas Wants Support for Guerrillas,", n.d. (Folder 21)
    - "Honoring Our China Treaty," New York Times, February 26, 1955 (Folder 22)
    - "A Medical Service Program to Aid the Middle Classes," (UNRRA-CNRRA in Shanghai), July 3, 1948 (Folder 23)
    - "A Memorandum to Americans Concerned With China,", April 12, 1951 (Folder 24)
    - Speech at Veterans Dinner to Commemorate the 5th Annni- versary of the 14th U.S. Air Force, Shanghai, March 10, 1948 (Folder 25)
    - "Sun Yat-sen to Me,", March 12, 1955 (Folder 26)
    - "Why Not Recognize Red China Even Now?", April 30, 1952 (Folder 27)
  - Mrochkovsky, E. S. (Folder 28)
  - Murayama, Masao (Folder 29)
  - Murphy, Rev. (Folder 30)
  - Murrow, Edward R. (Folder 31)
  - Muto, Nobuyoshi (Folder 32)
  - Nagai, Ryutaro (Folder 33)
  - Nagano, Osami (Folder 34)
  - Naggiar, Paul (Folder 35)
  - Nara, Takeji (Folder 36)
  - Narong, Luang Arch (Folder 37)
  - Nash, Ernest T. (Folder 38)
  - Nathan, Robert (Folder 39)
  - Navasvasti, Luang (Folder 40)
  - Ne-la-ko-erh-cha-pu (Folder 41)
  - New, Mrs. Wei-sheng (Folder 42)
  - Ni, Chih-liang (Folder 43)
  - Ni, Shih-ching (Folder 44)
  - Nichols, John (Folder 45)
  - Nieh, Yung-seng (Folder 46)
  - Niemoller, Dr. (Folder 47)
  - Ning, Hsiang-nan (Folder 48)
  - Niu, Yung-chien (Folder 49)
  - Noel, Frank (Folder 50)
  - Nomura, Tokie (Folder 51)
  - Norte, Dr. (Folder 52)
  - Nu, Thakin (Folder 53)
  - Oasa, Tadao (Folder 54)
  - Obama, Shigeru (Folder 55)
  - O'Bolger, R. E. (Folder 56)
  - O'Brien, M. M. (Folder 57)
  - Ochirbat, Bayan-Batoryn (Folder 58)
  - Odlun, Victor (Folder 59)
  - Office of Strategic Services Veterans
    - List of members, 1980 (Folder 60)
    - Newsletter, Winter, 1979 (Folder 61)
  - Ogata, Tagetora (Folder 62)
  - Oglu, Usuf bey (Folder 63)
  - Ogura, Masatsune (Folder 64)
  - Ohmura, Takuichi (Folder 65)
  - Ohsawa, Kikutaro (Folder 66)
  - Okazaki, Kazuo (Folder 67)
  - "Old Hands Status in Chungking," (Folder 68)
  - Old, William (Folder 69)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert (Folder 70)
  - Opper, Frederick (Folder 71)
  - Oram, Harold (Folder 72)
  - Orchard, William (Folder 73)
  - O'Ryan, John F. (Folder 74)
  - Ostananda, Nai Vilas (Folder 75)
  - Ott, Eugen (Folder 76)
  - Ouyang, Chen (Folder 77)
  - Overseas Chinese Anti-Communist Alliance (Folder 77A)
  - Overseas Economic Operations Task Force (Folder 78)
  - Ovidia, L. (Folder 79)
  - Oyama, Ikuo (Folder 80)
  - Paez, Jose (Folder 81)
  - Pak, Hon-yong (Folder 82)
  - Pan, Han-nien (Folder 83)
  - Pan, K. Y. Tong (Folder 84)
  - Pan, Stephen (Folder 85)
  - Panchen Erdeni (Folder 86)
  - Panchen Lama (Folder 87)
  - Pankey, Aubrey (Folder 88)
  - Pannikar, K. M. (Folder 89)
  - Paredes, Quinton (Folder 90)
  - Parker, Robert (Folder 91)
  - Parsons, Charles (Folder 92)
  - Patterson, Fritz O. (Folder 93)
  - Pattison, A. P. (Folder 94)
  - Paul, Yu-pin (Folder 95)
  - Pavry, Jal (Folder 96)
  - Pei, Tsu-yee (Folder 97)
  - Peng, Meng-chi (Folder 98)
  - Peng, Teh-Huai (Folder 99)
  - Petitt, Clifford (Folder 100)
  - Pfaff, Roger (Folder 101)
  - Phamonmontri, Nai (Folder 102)
  - Phanhonyothin, General (Folder 103)
  - Phelps, Dryden (Folder 104)
  - Phichit, Luang (Folder 105)
  - Piao, Kiang (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Pinthanon, C. (Folder 2)
  - Plotkin, George (Folder 3)
  - Poblete, Olga (Folder 4)
  - Popper, Martin (Folder 5)
  - Powell, John W. and Sylvia (Folder 6)
  - Powers, Francis Gary (Folder 7)
  - Pradit, Luang (Folder 8)
  - Pramoj, Mom Rajawongse (Folder 9)
  - Prapaut, Premyodhin (Folder 10)
  - Price, Frank (Folder 11)
  - Pu Yi, Henry (Folder 12)
  - Purpiss, Adams (Folder 13)
  - Pyun, Y. T. (Folder 14)
  - Quinn, John (Folder 15)
  - Quinto, Leon (Folder 16)
  - Quo, Tai-chi (Folder 17)
  - Rago, Vincent de (Folder 18)
  - Rajnava, Luang (Folder 19)
  - Ramos, Benigno (Folder 20)
  - Ravenholt, Albert (Folder 21)
  - Recto, Claro (Folder 22)
  - Redmond, Hugh F. (Folder 23)
  - Redmont, Bernard (Folder 24)
  - Reischauer, Edwin O. (Folder 25)
  - Reisini, Nicholas (Folder 26)
  - Reiss, Frederick (Folder 27)
  - Report from the Far East, n.d. (Folder 28)
  - Research prospects (Folder 29)
  - Reseda Files (Folder 30)
  - "Resumption of Normal Activities in China,", n.d. (Folder 31)
  - Rhame, John F. (Folder 32)
  - Ricarte, Artemio (Folder 33)
  - Rigney, Harold W. (Folder 34)
  - Riva, Tony (Folder 35)
  - Robert, Henri (Folder 36)
  - Roberts, Frank (Folder 37)
  - Robertson, Walter (Folder 38)
  - Robischon, Robert E. (Folder 39)
  - Roces, Andang (Folder 40)
  - Rodevitch, Maya (Folder 41)
  - Rogers, Theo (Folder 41A)
  - Romulo, Carlos (Folder 42)
  - Rosengrit, Luang (Folder 43)
  - Ross, Julia (Folder 44)
  - Ross, Stanley (Folder 45)
  - Rossi, Columbia (Folder 46)
  - Roth, Andrew (Folder 47)
  - Rothe (Folder 48)
  - Royere, M. (Folder 49)
  - Rubinstein, Sergei D. (Folder 50)
  - Russell, Maud (Folder 51)
  - Sabido, Pedro (Folder 52)
  - Saifudin (Azizov) (Folder 53)
  - Sahakorn, Luang (Folder 54)
  - Sakol, Prince (Folder 55)
  - Salisbury, Harrison (Folder 56)
  - Santos, Pedro (Folder 57)
  - Sargent, Clyde (Folder 58)
  - Sato, General (Folder 59)
  - Saw, U. (Folder 60)
  - Sayamkar, Luang (Folder 61)
  - Schultz, Benjamin (Folder 62)
  - Schuman, Frederick (Folder 63)
  - Schuman, Julian (Folder 64)
  - Sellett, George (Folder 65)
  - Sena, Phya Bahol (Folder 66)
  - Service, John S. (Folder 67)
  - Shanghai
    - Pre-, 1949 (Folder 68)
    - Post-, 1949
      - General (Folder 69)
      - British Chamber of Commerce (Folder 70)
      - Property owned by foreign nationals (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Shanghai Municipal Council, claims of former employees (Folder 2)
  - Shanghai Race Club (Folder 3)
  - Shanghai Recreation Fund (Folder 4)
  - Shanghai Volunteer Corps (Folder 5)
  - Shapiro, Sidney (Folder 6)
  - Shaw, Bruno (Folder 7)
  - Shaw, Vera (Folder 8)
  - Shen, Chang-huan (Folder 9)
  - Shen, Chin-ting (Folder 10)
  - Shen, Fa-chun (Folder 11)
  - Shen, Sampson (Folder 12)
  - Shen, Shih-hua (Folder 13)
  - Shen, Shih-yuan (Folder 14)
  - Shen, Te-hsieh (Folder 15)
  - Shen, Thomas C. (Folder 16)
  - Shen, Tsao-chih (Folder 17)
  - Shen, Tsung-han (Folder 18)
  - Sheng, Pi-Hua (Folder 19)
  - Sheng, Robert (Folder 20)
  - Shibusawa, Count (Folder 21)
  - Shibuya, Saburo (Folder 22)
  - Shidehara, Kijuro (Folder 23)
  - Shimada, Shigetaro (Folder 24)
  - Shiratori, Toshio (Folder 25)
  - Shiroido, Nagaikazu (Folder 26)
  - Shore, Donald (Folder 27)
  - Shu, Tzu-ching (Folder 28)
  - Shun Pao (Shanghai), 1943-45 (Folder 29)
  - Sidpsatrakom, Phla (Folder 30)
  - Sie, Cheou-kang (Folder 31)
  - Sileo, Columbia (Folder 32)
  - Simonov, K. (Folder 33)
  - Sison, Teofilo (Folder 34)
  - Smyth, William H. (Folder 35)
  - Sino-American Special Technical Cooperation Agreement, April 15, 1943 (Folder 36)
  - Slepak, I. V. (Folder 37)
  - Smedley, Agnes (Folder 38)
  - Smith, H. Maxcy (Folder 39)
  - Snow, Edgar (Folder 39A)
  - Sokolsky, George (Folder 40)
  - Songgram, Luang Bipul (Folder 41)
  - Songgram, Luang Chawengsak (Folder 42)
  - Songgram, Luang Dit (Folder 43)
  - Songgram, Luang Kat (Folder 44)
  - Songkram, Chaung (Folder 45)
  - Songkram, Luang Ehit (Folder 46)
  - Songkram, Han (Folder 47)
  - Soochow University, Friends of (Folder 48)
  - Soochow University Law School alumni (Folder 49)
  - Soong, Ching-ling (Madame Sun Yat-sen) (Folder 50)
  - Soong, T. V. (Folder 51)
  - Sopher, Arthur and Theodore (Folder 52)
  - Sorge, Wolfgang (Folder 53)
  - Soviet Union
    - General (Folder 54)
    - Inheritance law (Folder 55)
    - Law, general (Folder 56)
    - Law, general (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Propaganda (Folder 2)
  - Speeman, Michel (Folder 3)
  - Spemann, Kurt G. (Folder 4)
  - Ssu, Tu (Folder 5)
  - Ssu-tu, Mei-tong (Folder 6)
  - Stahmer, Heinrich von (Folder 7)
  - Standish, Myles (Folder 8)
  - Starobin, Joseph (Folder 9)
  - Stepanoff, Igor A. (Folder 10)
  - Stewart, Maxwell (Folder 11)
  - Stone, Chao Yung (Folder 12)
  - Stone, Martha (Folder 13)
  - Striso, Julius (Folder 14)
  - Strong, Anna Louise (Folder 15)
  - Stuart, Jim (Folder 16)
  - Stuart, John Leighton (Folder 17)
  - Suetsugu, Nobumasa (Folder 18)
  - Sugawara, Tatsuro (Folder 18A)
  - Sugiyama, General (Folder 19)
  - Sun Fo (Folder 20)
  - Sun, Li-jen (Folder 21)
  - Sutherland, Richard (Folder 22)
  - Sutton, G. W. (Folder 23)
  - Suzuki, Shigeo (Folder 24)
  - Suzuki, Yoshimichi (Folder 25)
  - Svasti, Subha (Folder 26)
  - Sylvester, John (Folder 27)
  - Sze, Alfred (Folder 28)
  - Sze, Fred C. (Folder 29)
  - Sze, Kenneth (Folder 30)
  - Tada, Hayao (Folder 31)
  - Tait, Eddie (Folder 32)
  - Takahashi, Sankichi (Folder 33)
  - Takamatsu, Prince (Folder 34)
  - Takebe, Rokuzo (Folder 35)
  - Takehisa, Tameji (Folder 36)
  - Takeuchi, Fumiakiri (Folder 37)
  - Tamiment Institute (Folder 38)
  - Tan, Kah-kee (Folder 39)
  - Tan, Lark-sye (Folder 40)
  - Tan, Wai-hsueh (Folder 41)
  - Tan, Yi-tzun (Folder 42)
  - Tanaka, Seichi (Folder 43)
  - Tanaka, Shizuichi (Folder 44)
  - Tanaka, Tetsusaburo (Folder 45)
  - Tang, T. C. (Folder 46)
  - Tani, Masayuki (Folder 47)
  - Tannebaum, Gerald (Folder 48)
  - Tao, Norman (Folder 49)
  - Tarbox, George Mack (Folder 50)
  - Tatischeff, Vladimir and Tautz, Sergei (Folder 51)
  - Taylor, Henry J. (Folder 52)
  - Taylor, L. K. (Folder 53)